{
    "subject": "resource/Maya_the_Honey_Bee",
    "predicate": "property/studio",
    "object": "resource/Nippon_Animation",
    "human_readable": "Maya the Honey Bee was produced by Nippon Animation.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9285117387771606,
            "question": "Who produced the animated series Maya the Honey Bee?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8153029680252075,
            "question": "What is the name of the animation studio that made Maya the Honey Bee?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6773502826690674,
            "question": "What country produced Maya the Honey Bee?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5153001546859741,
            "question": "What type of show is Maya the Honey Bee?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4770973324775696,
            "question": "Is Maya the Honey Bee a real bee?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4084303081035614,
            "question": "What is the main character's occupation in Maya the Honey Bee?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.37252047657966614,
            "question": "What are some common themes in Maya the Honey Bee?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.24356691539287567,
            "question": "Who are some of Maya the Honey Bee's friends?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.23217898607254028,
            "question": "Where can you watch episodes of Maya the Honey Bee?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.16697274148464203,
            "question": "Does Maya the Honey Bee have any popular catchphrases?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Maya the Honey Bee was produced by Nippon Animation.",
            "html": "dbpedia_9031_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Where can you watch episodes of Maya the Honey Bee?",
            "html": "dbpedia_9031_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Who are some of Maya the Honey Bee's friends?",
            "html": "dbpedia_9031_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What are some common themes in Maya the Honey Bee?",
            "html": "dbpedia_9031_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9031_100.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9031_2.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9031_23.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9031_24.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9031_26.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9031_27.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9031_42.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9031_54.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9031_64.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9031_89.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\n**Explanation:** The information across multiple documents clearly states that \"Maya the Honey Bee\" was produced by Zuiyo Enterprise, which later became Nippon Animation. This is evident from several entries in the provided context, such as those found in `88.txt`, `2.txt`, `23.txt`, and `63.txt`."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "The Most Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}